

# KATRINA C. ALEGRE

WEB DEVELOPER

# **OBJECTIVE**

I would like to contribute to your organization as a Web Developer, levering my ability to develop creative websites, develop E - Commerce web applications using readily available frameworks. With my passion for learning, I will be able to take part in empowering your team with my newly found coding expertise.

# **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Basic knowledge in Javascript, JQuery, PHP
- Basic knowledge in MySQL
- Adobe Illustrator
- Basic Photoshop
- Laravel Framework
- UI/UX
- Terminal and Command Line Interface
- Version Control GIT/ GITHUB
- Software Development Life Cycle
- Wireframing and Prototyping
- Debugging

# **EDUCATION**

# 480 HOURS OF INTESIVE WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE

TUITT Coding Bootcamp | Sept 2018 - Dec 2018

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Manila Central University - June 2004 - March 2008

### **CONTACT DETAILS**

85 Intan St. Bagong Barrio Caloocan City +639179711327 katrina.c.alegre@gmail.com Portfolio:https://katrinaalegre.github.io/ katrina-alegre/

# PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#### **TUITT CODING BOOTCAMP**

#### Capstone 3 - November 2018 - December 2018

- A Blog Site using Laravel Framework
- Users can Register, Login and Comment on a Blog using Disqus.
- Admin can Create, Retrieve, Update and Delete a Blog
- Environment: Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Javascript, JQery and Laravel

# Capstone 2 - October 2018 - November 2018

- An E Commerce website
- Users can Register, Login, buy products, pay through COD and PayPal, and receive confirmation email.
- Admin can Add new products, Update and Delete products, it can manage users and orders.
- Environment: Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Javascript and JQuery

#### Capstone 1 - September 2018 - October 2018

- A Static Website
- Website using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

# MEDICAL CLAIMS ANALYST Imagenet Philippines | May 2015 - July 2018

- Verifies, audits medical claims to ensure the accuracy of company reinbursement payments.
- Check for conflicts, errors or inconsistencies to the Health Insurance policies.

#### **DATA ANALYST**

#### Accenture Inc. | June 2009 - December 2012

- Verifying and updating information on submitted claims, reviewing the policy to determine which charges are eligible for reimbursement.
- Provides immediate resolution regarding issues in claims processing using different systems.